uhdwallpapers.org 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy

**What information is collected by blog?**   
I collect information from you when you subscribe to newsletter.   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on sites.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to site and other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**For what are used collected information?**   
Any of the information from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
• To personalize your experience in blog browsing   
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)   
• To improve blog   
(continually strive to improve my blog based on the visit information and feedback received from visitors)   
• To send periodic emails 

> The email address that you provide for feed subscription, WILL ONLY be used to send updates with the newest posts.

**Blog use cookies?**   
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.   
Use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that can offer better experiences and tools in the future. 

**Do I disclose any information to outside parties?**   
I DON'T sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information (as: web browser, IP, OS, etc.). 

**Third party links**   
Occasionally may include or offer third party services. Regarding these third party sites, they have separate and independent privacy policies. Therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**   
In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years old. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**   
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through this blog and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**   
By visiting my blog, you consent to blog privacy policy. 

**Contact form**   
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy contact me by email at the bellow email address:   
contact{at}uhdwallpapers{dot}org   
http://www.uhdwallpapers.org/
